[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The European company Diesel, producing jeans and other clothing, was founded in which country?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Albania", "Spain", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Lost Boys, the main characters move to which small coastal town in California?", "correct_answer": "Santa Carla", "incorrect_answers": ["Santa Fe", "Santa Barbara", "Santa Cruz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter, the largest planet in the Solar system, is the ruling planet of which astrological sign?", "correct_answer": "Sagittarius", "incorrect_answers": ["Aries", "Gemini", "Libra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The venomous lizard Gila monster was named after what?", "correct_answer": "The Gila River basin", "incorrect_answers": ["The Gila Expedition 1857", "Alberto Gilardino", "Gilligans Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the United States, firewood is usually sold by the cord. How big is a cord of wood?", "correct_answer": "128 cubic feet", "incorrect_answers": ["66 cubic feet", "66 feet", "128 square feet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The majority of filming for the 1978 comedy Animal House was done at what major US university?", "correct_answer": "University of Oregon", "incorrect_answers": ["Faber College", "UCLA", "Ohio State University"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city is the movie 8 Mile set?", "correct_answer": "Detroit, Michigan", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackson, New Jersey", "L.A. California", "Hudson, Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Miranda, Ariel, Umbriel, Titania, Oberon, Caliban, and Sycorax are names of the icy moons of this planet.", "correct_answer": "Uranus", "incorrect_answers": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During World War II, Paul Newman applied to become a fighter  pilot. Why was he rejected?", "correct_answer": "He was color blind.", "incorrect_answers": ["He did not pass the written test.", "He had an inner ear problem that affected his sense of balance.", "He was too short."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the name of Italy according to scientists who have studied its origin?", "correct_answer": "Land of young cattle", "incorrect_answers": ["Land of the holy water", "Land of the lamb", "Land of mountains"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All Bach flower remedies can be used by people.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What automobile manufacturer does Jack work for in the movie Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "A major one", "incorrect_answers": ["GM", "The one you just purchased a car from", "Ford"]}]